http://www.antillpark.com.au/privacy-policy

Members
ANTILL PARK COUNTRY GOLF CLUB LTD Privacy Policy   Version 1 - 4/03/2015 Antill Park Country Golf Club Ltd (APGC) understands the importance of privacy and is committed to complying with the National Privacy Principles (NPP) under the Privacy Act 1988 and the Privacy and Personal Information Protection Act 1998 which sets out how private sector organisations must treat "personal information". "Personal information" means information or opinions about an individual whose identity can be apparent or can reasonably be ascertained from that information. 1. What personal information does APGC collect? We will collect personal information about you, including your name, your title, your address, date of birth, gender and contact details. APGC will not collect personal information from you that is not needed. We may collect personal information about you from third parties eg people you work with, from public records and service providers. If you are a business service provider to APGC personal information about you including your name, company title and contact details may be collected. If you are making an application for employment, APGC will collect detailed personal information from you and may collect further information from referees and past employers you have authorised APGC to contact. 2. How APGC will use your personal information. APGC will use the personal information collected for the purposes that APGC disclose at the time the information is collected and as set out in this privacy policy. APGC will use your personal information for the provision of products and services and APGC business activities and interests. APGC may use information about you for marketing purposes and to keep you informed of Club activities and developments and to invite you to APGC events and functions. 3. How APGC may disclose your personal information. Generally we only use and disclose personal information about you for the purposes for which it was collected.APGC may disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the services you have asked APGC to provide. The third parties that APGC may disclose your personal information to include (but is not limited to) Golf NSW, Golf Australia and Golf Link. APGC may also disclose personal information about you to service providers that assist APGC in operating its general business. Where required or permitted by law, APGC will disclose other personal information about you. 4. The quality of the personal information APGC collects, uses and discloses. APGC continually reviews the information it collects, uses and discloses to ensure that it is accurate, complete and current. 5. How APGC keeps your information secure. APGC protects your personal information from unauthorised access, modification, use and disclosure.
Personal information held by APGC is kept in a secured environment whether that information is stored on paper or by an electronic means and we will take all reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information is stored safely to protect it from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure, including electronic and physical security measures. 6. How you can access personal information APGC holds about you. APGC will provide you with access to your personal information held subject to the exemptions provided under the Privacy Act which includes our obligations of confidentiality. APGC requires any request for access to your personal information to be in writing with the appropriate proof of identification and addressed to The Secretary, Antill Park Country Golf Club Limited, Jarvisfield Road, Picton, NSW 2571 or by emailing ‘admin@antillpark.com.au’ APGC will consider your request for access and within a reasonable time notify you if and/or when access can be granted. APGC will ordinarily not charge for the cost of providing access to your personal information. If APGC is required to decline your request for access we will provide you with reasons for our decision. If you seek to amend personal information that APGC hold you may contact us and we will correct any personal information that we agree is incorrect, incomplete or not current. If we do not agree with your requested amendments we will provide you with reasons for our decision. 7. Website Browsing The APGC website is a cookie-free site. Administration of the website records the site visits and logs the following information for statistical purposes: - your server address - the date and time of your visit to the site - pages accessed and documents downloaded - previous site visited - keywords used in search engines to find our site No attempt is however made to identify you or your browsing activities. 8. Links to other web sites Our web site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of linked web sites and so linked web sites are not subject to our privacy policies and procedures. 9. Changes to this Privacy Policy and Further Information on Privacy at APGC. This policy may be amended from time to time without notice. The current version of this Policy can be obtained by contacting the Secretary at APGC. If you require any further information, queries or complaints regarding APGC privacy or information handling practices please contact the APGC Secretary in writing addressed to Antill Park Country Golf Club Limited, Jarvisfield Road, Picton NSW 2571 or by emailing ‘admin@antill park.com.au’.
Golf Club: (02) 4677 1512 | Pro Shop: (02) 4677 1240
Back To Top
Antill Park Country Golf Club, Jarvisfield Road, Picton, NSW, 2571, Australia(02) 4677 1512admin@antillpark.com.au
Privacy Policy. Powered by Squarespace
